<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="array_of_citats">
        <item>An investment in knowledge always pays the best interest.</item>
        <item>Wisdom is knowing how little we know.</item>
        <item>The only thing in life achieved without effort is failure.</item>
        <item>Formal education will make you a living. Self-education will make you a fortune.</item>
        <item>A dream becomes a goal when action is taken toward its achievement.</item>
        <item>All would live long, but none would be old.</item>
        <item>Success is not in what you have, but who you are.</item>
        <item>All would live long, but none would be old.</item>
        <item>Success is not in what you have, but who you are.</item>
        <item>It’s easy to quit smoking. I’ve done it hundreds of times.</item>
        <item>Our greatest glory is not in never falling, but in getting up every time we do.</item>
        <item>Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much.</item>
        <item>To be conscious that you are ignorant is a great step to knowledge.</item>
        <item>English is not merely the medium of our thought; it is the very stuff and process of it.</item>
        <item>Being a woman is a terribly difficult task since it consists principally in dealing with men.</item>
        <item>To have another language is to possess a second soul.</item>
        <item>I am not young enough to know everything.</item>
        <item>A banker is a fellow who lends you his umbrella when the sun is shining, but wants it back the minute it begins to rain.</item>
        <item>Man invented language to satisfy his deep need to complain.</item>
        <item>If someone thinks that love and peace is a cliche that must have been left behind in the Sixties, that’s his problem. Love and peace are eternal. </item>
        <item>Money speaks sense in a language all nations understand.</item>
        <item>A candidate is someone who gets money from the rich and votes from the poor to protect them from each other.</item>
        <item>Facts are stubborn things, but statistics are more pliable.</item>
        <item>Not to know is bad, not to wish to know is worse.</item>
        <item>Success doesn’t come to you…you go to it.</item>
        <item>It does not matter how slowly you go so long as you do not stop.</item>
        <item>Silence propagates itself, and the longer talk has been suspended, the more difficult it is to find anything to say.</item>
        <item>Those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything.</item>
        <item>Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I’m not sure about the universe.</item>
        <item>Half of the American people have never read a newspaper. Half never voted for President. One hopes it is the same half.</item>
        <item>Every solution breeds new problems.</item>
        <item>Wealth is not his that has it, but his who enjoys it.</item>
        <item>An enemy is anyone who tells the truth about you.</item>
        <item>Believe that life is worth living, and your belief will help create the fact.</item>
        <item>The absent are always in the wrong.</item>
        <item>To make pleasures pleasant shorten them.</item>
        <item>Freedom is only good as a means; it is no end in itself.</item>
        <item>When Nature has work to be done, she creates a genius to do it.</item>
        <item>A lie begets a lie.</item>
        <item>When a man makes a woman his wife, it’s the highest compliment he can pay her, and it’s usually the last.</item>
        <item>We grow small trying to be great.</item>
        <item>Self-conquest is the greatest of victories.</item>
        <item>If you do not think about the future, you cannot have one.</item>
        <item>When all else is lost, the future still remains.</item>
        <item>Rather go to bed supperless than rise in debt.</item>
        <item>Future is purchased by the present.</item>
        <item>A benevolent man should allow a few faults in himself to keep his friends in countenance.</item>
        <item>He that is of opinion money will do everything may well be suspected of doing everything for money.</item>
        <item>Money often costs too much.</item>
        <item>Money is the fruit of evil as often as the root of it.</item>
        <item>Не does not possess wealth that allows it to possess him.</item>
        <item>Wealth is not his that has it, but his who enjoys it.</item>
        <item>The man who ain’t got an enemy is really poor.</item>
        <item>There is no little enemy.</item>
        <item>An enemy is anyone who tells the truth about you.</item>
        <item>Fools grow without watering.</item>
        <item>A fool can no more see his own folly than he can see his ears.</item>
        <item>Let us be thankful for the fools; but for them the rest of us could not succeed.</item>
        <item>A well-written life is almost as rare as a well-spent one.</item>
        <item>He that falls in love with himself will have no rivals.</item>
        <item>Being a woman is a terribly difficult task since it consists principally in dealing with men.</item>
        <item>Husband: what is left of the lover after the nerve has been extracted.</item>
        <item>The grand essentials of happiness are: something to do, something to love, and something to hope for.</item>
        <item>A lifetime of happiness! No man alive could bear it.</item>
        <item>"You may easily play a joke on a man who likes to argue – agree with him. "</item>
        <item>Beware of fury of a patient man.</item>
        <item>Nothing is as good as it seems beforehand.</item>
        <item>Debate is the death of conversation.</item>
        <item>A long dispute means both parties are wrong.</item>
        <item>The sounder your argument, the more satisfaction you get out of it.</item>
        <item>The people who make art their business are mostly impostors.</item>
        <item>Art has an enemy called ignorance.</item>
        <item>Nothing is beautiful from every point of view.</item>
        <item>Beauty is power; a smile is its sword.</item>
        <item>"He does it with a better grace, but I do it more natural. "</item>
        <item>Poverty wants some things, luxury many, avarice all things.</item>
        <item>By persistenly remaining single a man converts himself into a permanent public temptation.</item>
        <item>"Bachelors know more about women than married men; if they didn't, they'd be married too."</item>
        <item>It is human nature to think wisely and to act foolishly.</item>
        <item>A bachelor\'s life is a fine breakfast, a flat lunch, and a miserable dinner.</item>
        <item>"One person with a belief is equal to a force of ninety-nine who have only interest. "</item>
        <item>Charity: a thing that begins at home, and usually stays there.</item>
        <item>Not he who has much is rich, but he who gives much.</item>
        <item>The truly generous is the truly wise, and he who loves not otheres, lives unblest.</item>
        <item>Every charitable act is a stepping stone towards heaven.</item>
        <item>In the country of the blind the one-eyed man is king.</item>
        <item>A blind man will not thank you for a looking-glass.</item>
        <item>There\'s none so blind as they that won\'t see.</item>
        <item>Fortune befriends the bold.</item>
        <item>Who bravely dares must sometimes risk a fall.</item>
        <item>I\'d better give my life than be afraid to give it.</item>
        <item>We can\'t all be heroes because someone has to sit on the curb and clap as they go by.</item>
        <item>The greatest test of courage on earth is to bear defeat without losing heart.</item>
        <item>Every burnt book enlightens the world.</item>
        <item>Some books leave us free, and some books make us free.</item>
        <item>A book is a mirror; if an ass peers into it you can\'t expect an apostle to look out.</item>
        <item>The books that help you the most are those which make you think the most.</item>
        <item>Never read a book that is not an year old.</item>
        <item>Brevity is the soul of wit.</item>
        <item>Business is a combination of war and sport.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>